{
    "subject": "resource/Battle_of_the_Network_Stars",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/name",
    "object": "Battle of the Network Stars",
    "human_readable": "The name of Battle of the Network Stars is Battle of the Network Stars.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9869150519371033,
            "question": "Is 'Battle of the Network Stars' also known as 'Battle of the Network Stars'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9750381112098694,
            "question": "What is the name of the show Battle of the Network Stars?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8389765024185181,
            "question": "Could you give me a brief description of 'Battle of the Network Stars'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7919619083404541,
            "question": "What kind of competition is 'Battle of the Network Stars'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7493160367012024,
            "question": "Does the show title 'Battle of the Network Stars' reflect its theme?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7141754627227783,
            "question": "What type of participants are featured in 'Battle of the Network Stars'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6985610723495483,
            "question": "Has 'Battle of the Network Stars' been re-imagined or remade over time?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6888697743415833,
            "question": "Where could I find more information about 'Battle of the Network Stars'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6756801009178162,
            "question": "Is there any historical significance associated with 'Battle of the Network Stars'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6064503788948059,
            "question": "What are some popular elements or storylines commonly seen in 'Battle of the Network Stars'?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The name of Battle of the Network Stars is Battle of the Network Stars.",
            "html": "dbpedia_826_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any historical significance associated with 'Battle of the Network Stars'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_826_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where could I find more information about 'Battle of the Network Stars'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_826_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has 'Battle of the Network Stars' been re-imagined or remade over time?",
            "html": "dbpedia_826_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_826_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_826_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_826_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_826_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_826_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_826_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_826_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_826_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_826_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_826_89.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any more triples to evaluate! \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's my response:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`\n\nThe documents provided contain information about the show \"Battle of the Network Stars\", and it is stated in multiple files that its name is indeed \"Battle of the Network Stars\". Therefore, this triple is supported by the documents."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe provided documents all contain information about the show \"Battle of the Network Stars,\" confirming its alternative names and descriptions, thus supporting the statement that the name of Battle of the Network Stars is indeed Battle of the Network Stars."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}